Almost a whole Russian brigade may have been knocked out in the battle for vuh leads.
They've seen us!
Ukrainian soldiers are training with Leopard 2 and more and more experts agree:
The Russian big offensive is running.
Russia begins new offensives.
In Ukraine's neighboring Moldova, the president says
that a Russian coup was planned.
What does Russia have interest in the country?
"The War of the Week" deepens the latest news development in the Ukraine War.
The Ukrainian Army claims that they knocked out almost a whole brigade
of Russia's 155th lake infantry in the Battle of Vuhledar.
According to Ukraine, the Brigade must have consisted of 5,000 soldiers
As either killed, injured or captured, Politico writes.
If the 155th brigade has actually been beaten out
Is it a sign of how bloody battles are here right now.
In addition, this brigade is a kind of elite joint
Although it largely consists of recently mobilized soldiers.
and damaged Ukrainian infrastructure.
The latest information is that Russia actively builds its defense there.
It may point out that from a Russian point of view, an attempt is made from Ukrainian side
to win back land in the area as has become known
Not least because of the important nuclear power plant there.
Ukraine's neighboring Moldova has been in focus over the past week
After a Russian robot passed the country's airspace before it struck in Ukraine.
Moldavia is squeezed between Ukraine and Romania
And in the country there is the Russian -supported Breakthrough Republic Transnistria
As in the 1990s, independence from Moldova proclaimed.
No other countries recognize Transnistria as its own country.
But Russia has forces placed there
And the Council of Europe considers this as occupied Russian territory.
When Russia occupied parts of southern and eastern Ukraine during the war
Have you talked about a Landbro down to Transnistria.
For Moldova, this suddenly means that Russia
Which is not really a neighboring country, feels much closer.
Latest developments in the country was that Ukraine's President Zelenskyj claimed
that he discovered a Russian plan with the aim of "destroying Moldova".
Shortly thereafter, Moldavia's President accused Russia
for planning a coup attempt.
Russian plans to conduct subversive operations on our territory
Should they certainly save the lives of many soldiers and bring us closer to the victory.
Several countries have promised Leopard 2 to Ukraine
But it is still unclear when these deliveries will happen.
The first is expected to come within a couple of months.
But Germany has now criticized other European countries
for what one sees as a kind of inertia in sending
Compared to what it sounded like when doing these commitments.
For some European countries it is even unclear
What you have to send to Ukraine.
Information in the Wall Street Journal points to
That it can take up to two years for the United States to send its Abrams tanks.